A Guide to the Records of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship, 1926-1968
Library of Virginia
- License applications, 1926-1965
  - License applications, Jaw-Ji, 1934-1956 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Jo-Jul, 1934-1956 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Jum-Juv, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - License applications, K-Kh, 1933-1955 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Ki-Kn, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Ko-Ku, 1936-1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - License applications, La-Lam, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Lan-Lat, 1935-1957 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Lau-Laz, 1931-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Le-Lez, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Lew-Lis, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Lit-Ll, 1931-1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Lo-Los, 1936-1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Lot-Low, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Lu-Ly, 1934-1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - License applications, M-Mag, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Mah-Mam, 1935-1955 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Mana-Mank, 1932-1956 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Manl-Manw, 1934-1954 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Mar-Maz, 1935-1956 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Mc, 1935-1955 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Mea-Mem, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Men-Mex, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Mia-Mim, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - License applications, Min-Miss, 1934-1955 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - License applications, Mist-Mit, 1935-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Moa-Moo, 1934-1957 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Mop-Moz, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Mua-Muz, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - License applications, My-Myw, 1934-1957 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Na-Neh, 1934-1955 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Nei-Nh, 1934-1955 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Nia-Nix, 1933-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Noa-Nor, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Nos-Ny, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Oa-Ok, 1930-1957 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Ol-Om, 1934-1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - License applications, On, 1934-1957 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Op-Our, 1936-1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Out-Oz, 1934-1955 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Pa-Pap, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Par-Pas, 1936-1955 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Pat-Pg 1933-1956 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Ph, 1935-1955 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Pi-Pir, 1937-1956 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Pis-Pl, 1934-1956 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Po-Pow, 1934-1957 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Pr-Pri, 1935-1955 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Pr-Py, 1935-1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Q, 1934-1955 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Ra-Raim 1935-1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Rain-Raz, 1935-1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Re-Ree, 1934-1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Ref-Rev, 1935-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Rh-Ric, 1934-1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Rid, 1934-1957 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Rif-Riv, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - License applications, R0-Rob, 1935-1956 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Roc-Rom, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Roo-Roy 1934-1957 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Rua-Ruz, 1935-1956 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Sa-Saim, 1937-1954 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Sain-Sanf, 1935-1955 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Sang-Say, 1932-1956 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Sca-Scu, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Sea-Sek, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Sel-Sez, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Sha-She, 1934-1957 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - License applications, Sia-Sim, 1933-1956 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - License applications, Sin-Siz, 1933-1954 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - License applications, Sha-Shi, 1934-1956 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - License applications, Sho-Shu, 1931-1955 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Sia-Skir, 1935-1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Skit-Sl, 1932-1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Sm, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Sn-Som, 1934-1955 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Son-Song, 1926-1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Soo-Soy 1934-1955 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Sp-Spl, 1931-1955 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Spo-Spot, 1934-1955 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Spr-Sq, 1934-1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Sta-Stat, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Ste-Sto, 1934-1955 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Str, 1935-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Su-Sun, 1935-1954 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Sup-Swim, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Swin-Sy, 1935-1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Ta-Tas, 1934-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Tat-Tew, 1935-1956 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Tex-Tha, 1931-1955 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - License applications, The-Thin, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Thio-Tho, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Thra-Thrik, 1934-1956 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - License applications, Thril-Thy, 1933-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Ti-Tm, 1934-1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - License applications, To-Too, 1935-1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Top-Toy, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Tra-Trav, 1933-1956 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Tre-Ts, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Tu-Twi, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Two-Ty, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Ua-Unc, 1930-1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Und-Ut, 1931-1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Va-Ves, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Vi-Vo, 1932-1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Wa-Wap, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - License applications, War-Way, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - License applications, We, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Wha-Whep, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Wher-Whi, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Who-Why, 1933-1954 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Wia-Wil, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Wim-Wiz, 1934-1958 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Woa-Wooc, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Wood-Wu, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - License applications, X-Yi, 1934-1956 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - License applications, Yo-Z, 1932-1956 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - License applications, A-Ana, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Anc-Aw, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Ba-Bea, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Beb-Bey, 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Bi-Bli, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Blo-Boy, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Br-By, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Ca-Car, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Cas-Cav, 1942-1964 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Ce-Ci, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Cl-Co, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Cr-Cy, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Da-Dea, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Dec-Dew, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Df-Don, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Doo-Dy, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Ea-Ez, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Fa-Fin, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Fir-Fly, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Fo-Fra, 1957-1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Fre-Fu, 1956-1964 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Ga-Gip, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Gir-Giv, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Gl-Gred, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Gree-Gy, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Ha-Hei, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Hel-Hil, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Hip-Hm, 1957-1963 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Hoa-Hou, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - License applications, How-Hy, 1959-1965 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - License applications, I-Ip, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Ir-Iw, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Ja-Ju, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Ka-Kin, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Kip-Kro, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - License applications, La-Les, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Let-Lit, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Liv-Lop, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Lor-Lu, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Ma-Mail, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Main-Mar, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Mas-Mig, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Mis-Mur, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - License applications, Mus-My, 1955-1965 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - License applications, Na-Nie, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - License applications, Nif-Nit, 1957-1964 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - License applications, No-Nu, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - License applications, O-Op, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - License applications, Or-Oz, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Pa-Pea, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Pec-Pi, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Pl-Por, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - License applications, Pos-Py, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - License applications, Q, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - License applications, Ra-Ret, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - License applications, Rev-Ri, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - License applications, Roa-Rod, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - License applications, Rol-Rx, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - License applications, Sa-Sca, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - License applications, Sce-Shaf, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - License applications, Shag-Sig, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - License applications, Sil-Sk, 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - License applications, Sla-Som, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - License applications, Son-Spe, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - License applications, Spi-Steo, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - License applications, Step-Stri, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - License applications, Stro-Swa, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - License applications, Swe-Sy, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - License applications, Ta-Tee, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - License applications, Ten-The, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - License applications, Thi-Tho, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - License applications, Thr-Thu, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - License applications, Ti-To, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - License applications, Tr, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - License applications, Tu-Tw, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - License applications, Ua-Ut, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - License applications, Va-Vi, 1957-1964 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - License applications, Vir-Vo, 1957-1965 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - License applications, Wa-We, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - License applications, Wh-Wil, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - License applications, Win-Wom, 1956-1964 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - License applications, Won-Wyo, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - License applications, X-Z, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - License applications (Serials), A, 1935-1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - License applications (Serials), Ba-Blay, 1935-1956 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - License applications (Serials), Blaz-Burn, 1935-1956 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - License applications (Serials), Cal-Can, 1938-1962 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - License applications (Serials), Cap, 1936-1964 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - License applications (Serials), Capitol Films, 1946-1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - License applications (Serials), Car-Ch, 1946-1964 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - License applications (Serials), Cl-Com, 1937-1961 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - License applications (Serials), Con-Cus, 1936-1957 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - License applications (Serials), Da-Dau, 1936-1957 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - License applications (Serials), Dea-Dev, 1940-1950 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - License applications (Serials), Di, 1937-1959 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - License applications (Serials), Do-Du, 1934-1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - License applications (Serials), E, 1935-1949 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - License applications (Serials), Fa-Fi, 1935-1956 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - License applications (Serials), Fl-Fr, 1936-1951 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - License applications (Serials), Ga-Gm, 1942-1954 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - License applications (Serials), Goa-Gov, 1934-1951 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - License applications (Serials), Gra-Gre, 1935-1964 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - License applications (Serials), Gu, 1954-1963 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - License applications (Serials), Ha-Hom, 1933-1956 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - License applications (Serials), Hop-Hur, 1939-1957 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - License applications (Serials), I, 1939-1958 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - License applications (Serials), Ja-Je, 1942-1955 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - License applications (Serials), Jun-Juv, 1937-1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - License applications (Serials), K, 1933-1960 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - License applications (Serials), La-Lor, 1934-1944 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - License applications (Serials), Los-Lu, 1935-1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - License applications (Serials), Ma-Mar, 1934-1957 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - License applications (Serials), Mas-Mot, 1935-1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - License applications (Serials), Mov-Mys, 1934-1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - License applications (Serials), N, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - License applications (Serials), Newsreel, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - License applications (Serials), O, 1939-1953 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - License applications (Serials), Pa, 1937-1957 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - License applications (Serials), Pe-Ph, 1935-1956 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - License applications (Serials), Pi, 1934-1953 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - License applications (Serials), Po-Pu, 1935-1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - License applications (Serials), Q, 1939-1944 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - License applications (Serials), Ra-Res, 1934-1957 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - License applications (Serials), Ret-Rid, 1934-1955 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - License applications (Serials), Rin-Rus, 1935-1963 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - License applications (Serials), Sa-Sco, 1939-1949 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - License applications (Serials), Scr, 1934-1953 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - License applications (Serials), Se, 1941-1962 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - License applications (Serials), Sec, 1937-1953 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - License applications (Serials), Sk, 1937-1961 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - License applications (Serials), So, 1937-1960 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - License applications (Serials), Sp, 1934-1942 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - License applications (Serials), St, 1934-1942 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - License applications (Serials), Su, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - License applications (Serials), Ta-Te, 1934-1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - License applications (Serials), Thi-Thr, 1941-1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - License applications (Serials), Ti-Tr, 1937-1954 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - License applications (Serials), U, 1934-1957 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - License applications (Serials), V, 1934-1957 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - License applications (Serials), Wa-Wh, 1938-1948 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - License applications (Serials), Wi-Wo, 1936-1951 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - License applications (Serials), Z, 1952-1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Licenses regular and non-regular, 1954-1965
  This series contains two types of certificates, organized as Regular and Non-Regular Licenses. Both Regular and Non-Regular license certificates consists of two types of numbered forms. The license certificate entitled Licenses For Duplicates (Form 4) certifies that a motion picture studio is permitted to exhibit and display a film within the State of Virginia. The form contains the title of the movie, the date the certificate was issued, the amount of fee paid by the studio, serial number, print number and the signature of the Director of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship. The second form is entitled Copy of Application For Substitute Seal Original Receipted and Returned to Applicant (Form 8). This form gives the studio name, the title of the film, date issued and name of the Director. The form states that the movie studio is applying for a substitute seal to be attached to a print of the film previously censored and approved by the Division.
  The major difference between Regular and Non-Regular Licenses appears to be the arrangement order and time period. Regular Licenses are arranged by the prefix CS and cover the early 1950's to 1965 while the Non-Regular Licenses are arranged chronologically by serial number and cover the early 1960's.
  Arranged chronologically by serial number.
  - Licenses (Regular), Serial number record book, 1954-1965 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS5486-CS5600, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS5601-CS5800, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS5801-CS6000, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS6001-CS6200, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS6201-CS6400, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS6401-CS6600, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS6601-CS6800, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS6801-CS7000, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7001-CS7200, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7201-CS7400, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7401-CS7600, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7601-CS7800, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7801-CS7901, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS7902-CS8200, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS8201-CS8400, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS8401-CS8600, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS8601-CS8800, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS8801-CS9000, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS9001-CS9200, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS9201-CS9400, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS9401-CS9600, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS9601-CS9800, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS9801-CS10000, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10001-CS10200, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10201-CS10400, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS 10401-10600, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS 10601-10800, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS 10801-11000, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS 10001-10200, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10201-CS10400, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10401-CS10600, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10601-CS10800, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS10801-CS11000, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11001-CS11200, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11201-CS11258, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11259-CS11419, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11420-CS11598, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11599-11694, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11695-CS11800, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS11801-CS12000, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS12001-CS12200, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS12201-CS12400, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS12401-CS12600, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS12601-CS12800, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS12801-CS13000, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS13001-CS13200, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS13201-CS13400, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS13401-CS13600, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS13601-CS13800, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS13801-CS14000, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS14001-CS14200, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS14201-CS14400, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS14401-CS14600, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS14601-CS14800, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS14801-CS15000, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS15001-CS15200, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS15201-CS15400, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS15401-CS15600, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS15601-CS15800, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS15801-CS16000, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16001-CS16200, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16201-CS16281, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16282-CS16400, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16401-CS16600, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16601-CS16800, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS16801-CS17000, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS17001-CS17200, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS17201-CS17400, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS17401-CS17600, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS17601-CS17800, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS17801-CS18000, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS18001-CS18200, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS18201-CS18400, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS18401-CS18600, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS18601-CS18800, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS18801-CS19000, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS19001-CS19200, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS19201-CS19400, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS19401-CS19600, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS19601-CS19800, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS19801-CS20000, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS20001-CS20200, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS20201-CS20400, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Licenses (Regular), CS20401-CS20600, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)